<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE Rule PUBLIC "sailpoint.dtd" "sailpoint.dtd">
<Rule language="beanshell" name="Before Rule" type="WebServiceBeforeOperationRule">
  <Description>This rule is used by the  Web Services connector before performing any operation like testconnection, aggregation etc. Here user can update the existing Endpoint object using a key 'updatedEndPoint' and along with it save 
required attribute in the application using key 'connectorStateMap'. If user just want to return Endpoint (requestEndPoint) no need to create map and update the key values. But if a user wants to return both Endpoint (requestEndPoint) and connectorStateMap who's values will be eventually saved in the application. Create a Map and add both using respective key's.</Description>
  <Signature returnType="Object">
    <Inputs>
      <Argument name="log">
        <Description>
          The log object associated with the SailPointContext.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="context">
        <Description>
          A sailpoint.api.SailPointContext object that can be used to query the database if necessary.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="application">
        <Description>The application whose data file is being processed.</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="requestEndPoint">
        <Description>The current request information contain header, body, context url, method type, response attribute map, 
                successful response code
                </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="oldResponseMap">
        <Description>earlier response object </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="restClient">
        <Description>REST Client Object</Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="provisioningPlan">
        <Description>provisioningPlan can be used to update the payload of the http request. Provisioning Plan has an account request which defines the operation to be performed on the account.
                 An account request can contain multiple attributes requests and each attribute request represents an operation on a single account attribute.
                </Description>
      </Argument>
    </Inputs>
    <Returns>
      <Argument name="Endpoint or Updated Map which contains requestEndPoint and connectorStateMap">
        <Description>Updated Endpoint or information Map which contains endpoint and connectorStateMap</Description>
      </Argument>
    </Returns>
  </Signature>
  <Source>System.out.println("requestEndPoint"+requestEndPoint);

Map updatedMap = new HashMap();
for(Map iterateMap :processedResponseObject){

   System.out.println(iterateMap.get("employeeID"));


 List empIds = iterateMap.get("employeeID");

for(String emp:empIds ){

System.out.println("emp"+emp);

System.out.println("emp"+emp.substring(1));

emp = emp.substring(1);

iterateMap .put("employeeID",emp);
}

}
  updatedMap.put("data",processedResponseObject);

return updatedMap;



</Source>
</Rule>