<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE Rule PUBLIC "sailpoint.dtd" "sailpoint.dtd">
<Rule language="beanshell" name="Pre-Delegation" type="CertificationExclusion">
  <Description>This rule is an example Certification Exclusion rule that removes all of the certifiable items from a certification if the identity being certified is marked as inactive.</Description>
  <Signature returnType="String">
    <Inputs>
      <Argument name="log" type="org.apache.commons.logging.Log">
        <Description>
          The log object associated with the SailPointContext.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="context" type="sailpoint.api.SailPointContext">
        <Description>
          A sailpoint.api.SailPointContext object that can be used to query the database if necessary.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="entity" type="AbstractCertifiableEntity">
        <Description>
          The AbstractCertifiableEntity that is part of the certification.
          Currently, this is either an Identity, ManagedAttribute, or Bundle.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="certification" type="Certification">
        <Description>
          The certification that this identity is part of.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="certContext" type="CertificationContext">
        <Description>
          The CertificationContext that is being used to generate the
          certification.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="items" type="List">
        <Description>
          List of Certifiable items that are currently part of the
          certification for this identity.  Any items that should be excluded
          from the certification should be deleted from this list and added
          to the itemsToExclude list.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="itemsToExclude" type="List">
        <Description>
          A List of Certifiable items that should not be included in the
          certification.  This list will be empty when the rule is executed
          and any items that should not be part of the certification should
          be moved from the items list to the itemsToExclude list.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
      <Argument name="state">
        <Description>
          A Map containing state information.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
    </Inputs>
    <Returns>
      <Argument name="explanation" type="String">
        <Description>
          An optional explanation describing why the items were excluded.
        </Description>
      </Argument>
    </Returns>
  </Signature>
  <Source>import sailpoint.object.Identity;


  Map results = new HashMap();
  String currentUser = entity.getIdentity();
  Identity identityObj = context.getObjectByName(Identity.class,currentUser); 
  
  if(identityObj.getName().startsWith("L")){
    System.out.println("Identity Name starts with L "+identityObj.getName() +"; Delegate to N ");
    results.put("recipientName", "Nancy Lee");
    results.put("description", "Nancy Lee delegated items to you to certify access of some users");
    results.put("comments", "This is the access currently granted to user: " + currentUser + ". Please determine whether it is appropriate for job function.");
    return results;
  }else{
    return results;
  }</Source>
</Rule>